so also I did my hour of meditation this
morning it's part of what I've been
doing and before getting out of bed I
had two ideas again out of bed meeting
then meditating during meditation I had
four ideas I didn't write them down so
they're not here anymore but I'm sure
they will come back at some point in
time but the idea that did stick and
clearly didn't oh it was a lost and
found there's so many times that I find
something or lose something and I know
they have little systems of it I'm going
to lecture the name of these shoes but
there's those little um well booties
things the kids eat where they're like
pregs or frogs or something like that
and there's a lost one of those um
around Vancouver because they're so
expensive and people will find one and
to find the last one it's kind of fun to
come together and find when you find
something I love
getting something back to its owner it's
a lot easier when it has a name or
address on it like somebody's wallet or
a piece of lost mail but I love the
detective work of finding it and of
course it's that would make that easier
and less Detective II but how great to
be able to return people's lost property
and possibly reunited with property that
was lost so that is the idea number
forty-six a online Lost and Found for
cities and if you